<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>The Greening of Isaac: Regreen'd</name>
    <directory>greenisaac</directory>
    <id>2962067544</id>
    <description>Have you ever wanted to play your favourite crying infant, but coloured green? IF so, then this mod is for you!!!

[h1][b]Features[/b][/h1]
Currently, the mod adds 2 characters: Green Isaac and Green Cain, along with 10+ unlockable items you can find in normal pools and 60+ &quot;green&quot; items you can find! It also adds 2 new pickups and 6 new consumables you can unlock!
[b]THE MOD ALSO ADDS 2 CHALLENGES (in the custom challenge menu)!!!!!![/b]

The mod also has full [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872]EID[/url] support.
The mod also contains a built-in Dead Sea Scrolls menu, where you can manage and see your unlocks, and see descriptions of all of the mod's items!

[h1][b]Green Isaac[/b][/h1]
With his G6 and his gardening mastery, he can reroll any item into one of his special [b]&quot;green&quot; items[/b]! These green items can be anything from a vegetable to a bundle of grass clippings, and each of them have their own zany effects!
His pool initially consists of about 50 items, but by beating bosses you can unlock add about 10 more items to the pool!

[h1][b]Green Cain[/b][/h1]
Starting with the Green Sack, a holding bag of sorts, he can magically pull out custom slot machines to gamble to his heart's content, receiving aid from his buddies and the new consumables added in the mod!

[h1][b]Unlocks[/b][/h1]
Getting post-it marks as Green Isaac unlocks more items in his &quot;green&quot; pool, along with unlocking the G6 upon defeating Delirium! As Green Cain, you unlock new items, consumables and pickups for getting marks!

[h1][b]Commands[/b][/h1]
[list]
[*][b]gr_unlockall[/b] - Unlocks all of the mod's content, restart your run for the changes to take effect.
[*][b]gr_reset[/b] - Resets all of the mod's unlocks, restart your run for the changes to take effect.
[/list]

[hr][/hr]
This mod is an expansion on the April Fools mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2955925985]Jezreel[/url].

[h3][b]Credits[/b][/h3]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198220130431/]spoop[/url] - Coder, helper spriter
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561199023186369/]Split[/url] - Spriter for the majority of the mod's content
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198225074544/]Nihil[/url] - Musician

[b]DejuiceTD[/b] - Moral support

[b]Special Thanks![/b]
[list]
[*]Foks,
[*]GentleSin
[*]Monwil,
[*]Ferpe,
[*]linedime,
[*]wons,
[*]ratratrat,
[*]caligulasAquarium,
[*]meojo
[/list]

[h2][b]PLEASE REPORT BUGS IN THE BUG REPORT DISCUSSION OR DM ME ON DISCORD AT [u]spooptr[/u][/b][/h2]
[h2][b]BUG REPORT COMMENTS [u]WILL BE DELETED[/u][/b][/h2]</description>
    <version>2.9.3</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Bosses"/>
    <tag id="Challenges"/>
    <tag id="Shaders"/>
</metadata>
